streetfire.net 2011-05-11

# CarDomain Network, Inc. – Privacy Policy — CarDomain Network

**Last Revision: September 30, 2010**

CarDomain wants to make it easy for you to understand its information collection practices. You are probably sick of the legalese that companies put in their privacy policies. We are too. So we decided to revise our privacy policy to be in plain English.

  * What Categories of Information Does CarDomain Collect and How Does it Typically Use This Information?
  * Can I Control How CarDomain Uses the Information It Collects?
  * Do CarDomain’s Advertisers, Vendors, or Business Partners Collect Information About Me?
  * Does CarDomain Share the Information it Collects With Others?
  * How Secure Is My Personal Information?
  * What About The Children?

Our Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect from you when you use CarDomain’s websites, services, and applications (the “Services”) and how we use such information. By using the Services, you agree to this policy. We may change or update this policy from time to time. Any updated policy shall be effective after it is posted.

If you have any questions about this policy, write to 849 S. Broadway, UNIT 802, Los Angeles, CA 90014 or send email to privacy[@]cardomain.com.

* * *

There are three categories of information which we may obtain in the course of our relationship with you. These are described below, along with a description of how we may use such information. Note: our use of information is subject to exceptions (e.g., we may disclose Personal Information in response to a subpoena) which are discussed in the Section titled “Does CarDomain Share the Information it Collects With Others?”

  * User Contributed Information.Information you voluntarily post, upload, or display to other Service users through the Services is “User Contributed Information”. For example, the information on your Ride Page is User Contributed Information. **USE OF USER CONTRIBUTED INFORMATION** : Our use of this information is straight-forward — we publish it in accordance with any privacy settings in your account. However, you should assume that this information will be accessible by anyone. By using our Services, you agree that we can use the User Contributed Information in accordance with this policy and in accordance with our terms of service.
  * Personal Information.Information that you provide us when using the Service which (i) is not provided for publication or display through the Services and (ii) identifies you by full name, full postal address, phone number, or email address, or includes information necessary to process payment for the Service, such as a credit card number, expiration date and billing address, is “Personal Information.” For example, you may provide Personal Information such as an email address when you register to use certain Services. **USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION** : We will not reveal your Personal Information to other Service users unless you authorize it. We will not sell your Personal Information or share your Personal Information with others. Again, we may use Personal Information for the purposes for which it was provided, such as to process transactions, identify you as an account-holder, or send you an email.
  * General Information.”General Information” is information that you  
provide us or which we collect which is not Personal Information (e.g., information about your computer or browser, or age and gender information you provide when filling out a survey). For example, we may collect General Information about your computer (Mac or PC), web browser, Internet Protocol (IP) address and the date and time of your visit. We may use cookies, web beacons and GPS software to collect General Information. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We may use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. Normally, these cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. We may use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID to make it easier for you to login when you come back to use the Service. You may be able to remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature. A web beacon is a small graphic files used to determine if a page has been viewed. If you use the Service on a GPS-enabled mobile device, we may collect the city and state and other information provided by GPS. **USE OF GENERAL INFORMATION** : We may use General Information to understand how people use our Services. We may use cookies to keep you logged in to your account, track your use of our Services, or to prevent you from entering the same information repeatedly.

You can use many of our Services without submitting User ContributedInformation. If you submit User Contributed Information, we typically allow you to choose how or when we publish User Contributed Information. We may send you marketing messages to any email address you provide us. You can choose not to receive any marketing email from us by following the instructions to “unsubscribe” provided in the email. You can also log in to your account to unsubscribe from receiving marketing email.

  * Sites we do not own or operate.The Services may contain or link to features and content on websites we do not own or operate. These websites may collect information about you, but we do not have control over their collection practices. If you are visiting a third-party website, please review its privacy policy.
  * Advertisers.We may use third-party advertising companies and networks to serve ads through our Services. These companies and networks may collect and use General Information to deliver more relevant advertising to you, and for other business purposes. For example, if you conduct a search for a certain type of car, you may see advertisements for this type of car on your next visit to a CarDomain website. For more information or to opt-out of receiving targeted advertising from third-party advertising companies and networks, go to  <http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>. Also keep in mind that if you enter information into a form through an advertisement, or visit a Website depicted in an advertisement, any information you provide may be provided to the advertiser. The advertiser’s privacy policies may differ from our policy.

Note: BlueKai, a third party, uses cookies to collect General Information from you when you access the CarDomain website and Services.  Blue Kai may use this information in order to tailor advertisements on this and other websites about goods and services that might be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Blue Kai, click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

If you would like to see what General Information Blue Kai has collected about your internet usage, and have the opportunity to edit that information, please click here. <http://www.bluekai.com/registryoverview.html>.

Note: We have contracted with Lotame Solutions LLC (”Lotame”) to better help us operate the website, report website traffic, statistics, advertisement ‘click-throughs’, and/or other activities on our web site. Lotame may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. Lotame does not collect personally identifiable information. For more information about how the information is collected and used by Lotame, please see Lotame’s privacy policy at <http://www.lotame.com/privacy/>.

Note: As part of our membership in the NAI, ValueClick Media has updated its Publisher Terms & Conditions, which require you to adhere to the 2008 NAI Principles. You will need to ensure that you comply with your obligations set forth in the 2008 NAI Principles, including without limitation, revising your web site(s)’ privacy policy(ies) to include, without limitation, the following:

  * Notice as to the nature and scope of the collection and use of information gathered by you and any of your business partners, including third party ad networks on any of your web sites; and
  * Choice to an Internet user of any of your web sites to opt-out from such information collection and use, including a clear link to the NAI’s opt-out page at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://news.valueclickmedia.com/rd4/ck/13205-82055-17336-8?m=4-366&e=hac3fbbec7b).

Note: We have contracted with ValueClick Media (“ValueClick”) to serve ands and collect General Information from you when you access the CarDomain website and Services. ValueClick may use this information in order to provide advertisements on this and other websites about goods and services that might be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by ValueClick, click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. ****

From time to time we may need to disclose the information subject to this policy to other people, entities, or government authorities. For example:

  * Internal business purposes.We may share information we collect with third parties to complete transactions you have requested or to perform services on our behalf. Third parties who perform services on our behalf are obligated to use the information for the purpose it was provided.
  * You authorize it.We may disclose your Private Information if you authorize it. Sometimes, your authorization may be implicit. For example, if you use our Service to send a message to someone, we will forward your message to the intended recipient.
  * To protect ourselves or others.We disclose information we collect when we make the good faith determination that it is appropriate to comply with the law (e.g., a subpoena or court order); to enforce or apply this policy, or our other policies or agreements; to initiate, render, bill, or collect for amounts owed to us; to protect our or our users’ rights, property, or safety; to protect our users from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful use of the Services; or if we reasonably believe that otherwise exigent circumstances require or justify disclosure of this information.
  * Business transfers.Information about you, including Private Information, may be disclosed or transferred wholesale as part of any merger, acquisition, debt financing, or sale of company assets, as well as in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy, or receivership (in which information could be transferred to third parties as one of our business assets).
  * Site usage.We may use third-parties to help measure the effectiveness of our advertising and to analyze usage of the Services. Third parties may help us analyze General Information we obtain from you (we generally place restrictions on those third parties’ use of such information). Our third party analytic partners may use the General Information for their business purposes, such at to report aggregate, non-Personal Information about the use of their services and technologies in connection with the Services.

We use reasonable security measures to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized use and disclosure while in our control. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption to protect certain Personal Information, such as credit card information, that is transmitted over the Internet. However, no security measures are perfect, and we cannot guarantee that any information we collect will be secure from unauthorized access or use.

Our Services are not intended for children under the age of 16, or anyone who is under the age of majority who does not have the consent of their parent or legal guardian. We do not knowingly publish information for anyone under 16 years old through our Services. If you know of anyone under the age of 16 whose information is published through our Services, or have other concerns about children’s privacy, please write to us at childrensprivacy[@]cardomain.com.

**Magnetic Media Online, Inc.**

Note:  Magnetic Media Online, Inc. (“Magnetic”), a third party, uses cookies to collect General Information from you when you access the CarDomain Network’s websites and Services.  Magnetic may use this information in order to tailor advertisements on this and other websites about goods and services that might be of interest to you.  Magnetic may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. Magnetic does not collect personally identifiable information. For more information about how the information is collected and used by Magnetic, please see Magnetic’s privacy policy at <http://www.magnetic.is/consumer-privacy/>.  For opt-out instructions from Magnetic, please visit <http://domdex.com/w3c/optout.html>.  If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Magnetic, click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>
